Guide to the Human Rights Watch records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series 2: Country Files, 1978-1997
  - "Laws for Correction and Rehabilitation of Offenders", undated (Box 442, Folder 24)
  - New material brought back, 1995 (Box 442, Folder 25)
  - Prison--General
  - ABC "20/20" Transcripts, 1992 (Box 442, Folder 26)
  - Amnesty International (AI), 1994 (Box 442, Folder 27)
  - Clippings, 1991-1995 (Box 442, Folder 28)
  - Death Row and Death Penalty, 1993-1994 (Box 442, Folder 29)
  - "Prison Conditions in Japan (1994)", 1994 (Box 442, Folder 30)
  - "Prison Litigation in Japan", 1994 July (Box 442, Folder 31)
  - Prison Rules, 1994 (Box 442, Folder 32)
  - Sano Case, 1994 (Box 442, Folder 33)
  - Sawachi Case, 1991 (Box 442, Folder 34)
  - Trip Related, 1994
  - Japan Logistics, 1994 (Box 442, Folder 35)
  - Names and Addresses, 1993-1994 (Box 442, Folder 36)
  - Official Contacts, 1994 (Box 442, Folder 37)
  - Supporting Group for Mr. Isoe, 1995 (Box 442, Folder 38)
  - Trade and Aid, 1988-1990 (Box 442, Folder 39)
  - Trade Unions/Labor Rights, 1989-1990 (Box 442, Folder 40)
  - United States--Relations, 1990-1992 (Box 442, Folder 41)
  - Women, 1988 1990 (Box 442, Folder 42)
  - Zhenhai, Zhang--Legal Documents, 1989-1990 (Box 442, Folder 43)
  - Laos
  - Asia Watch (AW)--Correspondence, 1990 (Box 442, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence, 1984-1991 (Box 442, Folder 45)
  - Lao Human Rights Council, 1994 (Box 442, Folder 46)
  - Press Clippings, 1990-1993, (2 folders) (Box 442, Folder 47-48)
  - Maldives--United States--Department of State--Country Report, 1989 (Box 442, Folder 49)
  - Malaysia (Box 443)
  - Aliran Monthly, 1988-1993, (7 folders) (Box 443, Folder 1-7)
  - Asia Watch (AW)
  - Correspondence, 1989-1992, (2 folders) (Box 443, Folder 8-9)
  - Work, 1989-1990 (Box 443, Folder 10)
  - Committee for Chilean Inquiry (CCI), 1988-1989 (Box 443, Folder 11)
  - Commonwealth--Heads of Government, 1989 (Box 443, Folder 12)
  - Communication with Malaysia, 1991-1992 (Box 443, Folder 13)
  - Consumers Association of Penang (CAP), 1990 (Box 443, Folder 14)
  - Contacts, 1989 (Box 443, Folder 15)
  - Corporal Punishment, 1979 1989 1991 (Box 443, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 1988-1994, (3 folders) (Box 443, Folder 17-19)
  - Death Sentences, 1989-1991 (Box 443, Folder 20)
  - Demonstrations, 1989 (Box 443, Folder 21)
  - Drugs, 1989 1991-1992 (Box 443, Folder 22)
  - Economy, 1989-1990 (Box 443, Folder 23)
  - Education, 1989 (Box 443, Folder 24)
  - Elections, 1989-1990 (Box 443, Folder 25)
  - Fernandez, Irene--Trial, 1996 (Box 443, Folder 26)
  - Foreign Relations, 1989-1992, (2 folders) (Box 443, Folder 27-28)
  - Freedom of Expression, 1988-1990 (Box 443, Folder 29)
  - General, 1989-1993, (4 folders) (Box 443, Folder 30-33)
  - Government, 1989-1992 (Box 443, Folder 34)
  - Human Rights Organizations, 1988-1989 (Box 443, Folder 35)
  - Human Rights Violations, 1988-1989 (Box 443, Folder 36)
  - Internal Security Act (ISA), 1987-1991 (Box 443, Folder 37)
  - Killings, 1991 (Box 443, Folder 38)
  - Labor, 1989-1990 (Box 443, Folder 39)
  - Land Issues, 1989-1992, (2 folders) (Box 443, Folder 40-41)
  - Legal System/Texts, 1988-1990 (Box 443, Folder 42)
  - Manjeet Singh--Case, 1989-1990 (Box 443, Folder 43)
  - Military, 1989 (Box 443, Folder 44)
  - Missions/Visits, 1989 1991, (3 folders) (Box 443, Folder 45-47)
  - National Front, 1989 (Box 443, Folder 48)
  - New Economic Plan (NEP), 1989 (Box 443, Folder 49)
  - Political Opposition
  - Abuses, 1989-1990 (Box 443, Folder 50)
  - General, 1989-1992, (2 folders) (Box 443, Folder 51-52)
  - Press, 1989-1995, (12 folders) (Box 444, Folder 1-12)
  - Prisons/Prisoners
  - General, 1989 1991 (Box 444, Folder 13-14)
  - Prisoner Releases, 1988-1989 (Box 444, Folder 15)
  - Racial Issues/Language, 1989 (Box 444, Folder 16)
  - Refugees
  - Aceh Province, 1990-1991, (2 folders) (Box 444, Folder 17-18)
  - Push-offs, 1990-1992, (2 folders) (Box 444, Folder 19-20)
  - Religion, 1989-1990 (Box 444, Folder 21)
  - Sabah, 1989-1994, (4 folders) (Box 444, Folder 22-25)
  - Sarawak
  - Arrests, 1989 (Box 444, Folder 26)
  - General, 1987-1992, (5 folders) (Box 444, Folder 27-31)
  - Protests, 1990 (Box 444, Folder 32)
  - Scandals/Corruption, 1989 (Box 444, Folder 33)
  - Sultan Azlan Shah (King of Malaysia), 1989 (Box 444, Folder 34)
  - Torture, 1989-1990 (Box 444, Folder 35)
  - Trade and Aid, 1989-1990 (Box 444, Folder 36)
  - Tribal/Ethnic Groups, 1989 undated (Box 444, Folder 37)
  - United Malays National Organization (UMNO), 1989 (Box 444, Folder 38)
  - United States
  - Bush Report, 1989 (Box 444, Folder 39)
  - Congressional Advocacy, 1988-1989 (Box 444, Folder 40)
  - Mongolia
  - General, 1989-1992, (4 folders) (Box 444, Folder 41-44)
  - Reports, 1990-1992 (Box 444, Folder 45)
  - Nepal
  - Amnesty International (AI)--Reports, 1993-1994 (Box 444, Folder 46)
  - Asia Watch (AW)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 444, Folder 47)
  - Work, 1989-1995, (4 folders) (Box 444, Folder 48-51)
  - Centre for the Victims of Torture, 1992-1994 (Box 444, Folder 52)
  - Chron. Files, 1990-1995, (5 folders) (Box 445, Folder 1-5)
  - Contacts, 1990-1991 (Box 445, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence
  - General, 1989-1992 1994-1995, (3 folders) (Box 445, Folder 7-9)
  - Government, 1990 (Box 445, Folder 10)
  - Foreign Relations, 1990 (Box 445, Folder 11)
  - Forum for Protection of Human Rights (FOPHUR), 1992-1994 (Box 445, Folder 12)
  - General, 1987-1992, (5 folders) (Box 445, Folder 13-17)
  - Human Rights Violations in Nepal: An Asia Watch Report, 1989 August (Box 445, Folder 18)
  - Current Information, 1989 (Box 445, Folder 19)
  - Pre-1990 Information, 1988-1989 (Box 445, Folder 20)
  - Report, 1989 (Box 445, Folder 21)
  - Missions, 1990 1992-1995, (5 folders) (Box 445, Folder 22-26)
  - "Rape for Profit: Trafficking of Nepali Girls and Women to India's Brothels"--Background Material, 1995, (4 folders) (Box 445, Folder 27-30)
  - Working File, 1990 (Box 446, Folder 1)
  - New Caledonia
  - Front Uni de Liberation Kanak (FULK), 1988-1989 (Box 446, Folder 2)
  - General, 1989-1990 (Box 446, Folder 3)
  - North Korea
  - Asia Watch (AW)
  - Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 446, Folder 4)
  - Work, 1988-1990 (Box 446, Folder 5)
  - North-South Relations, 1988-1990 (Box 446, Folder 6)
  - Papers--Miscellaneous, 1988-1989 (Box 446, Folder 7)
  - Press, 1985-1991, (3 folders) (Box 446, Folder 8-10)
  - Pacific Islands--General, 1989-1992 (Box 446, Folder 11)
  - Pakistan
  - Ahmadiyya Movement in Islam, 1987-1989 (Box 446, Folder 12)
  - Amnesty International (AI), 1995 (Box 446, Folder 13)
  - Asia Watch (AW)--Work, 1993 1995 (Box 446, Folder 14)
  - Chron. Files, 1990-1991 1993-1995, (5 folders) (Box 446, Folder 15-19)
  - Communication with Government, 1994-1995 (Box 446, Folder 20)
  - Foreign Relations, 1989-1992 (Box 446, Folder 21)
  - Freedom of Expression, 1994-1995 (Box 446, Folder 22)
  - General
  - Background, 1989-1990 1993 (Box 446, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1992 1994-1995, (2 folders) (Box 446, Folder 24-25)
  - Human Rights Commission of Pakistan (HRCP)
  - I.A. Rehman, 1993-1994 (Box 446, Folder 26)
  - Quarterly Newsletter, 1994 (Box 446, Folder 27)
  - Legal System/Texts, undated (Box 446, Folder 28)
  - Military and Government, 1989-1992, (2 folders) (Box 446, Folder 29-30)
  - Mohajir Qoumi Movement (MQM) (Overseas), 1989-1990 1993-1995, (2 folders) (Box 446, Folder 31-32)
  - NGOs/HR Organizations, 1994-1995 (Box 447, Folder 1)
  - Pakistan/Afghanistan Mission, 1990 (Box 447, Folder 2)
  - Political Opposition, 1988-1991 (Box 447, Folder 3)
  - Publications--Miscellaneous, 1993-1995 (Box 447, Folder 4)
  - Question and Answer Series, 1995 June (Box 447, Folder 5)
  - Trade and Aid, 1989-1992 (Box 447, Folder 6)
  - United Nations, 1993-1994 (Box 447, Folder 7)
  - United States
  - Congressional Advocacy, 1988-1989 (Box 447, Folder 8)
  - Policy, 1994 (Box 447, Folder 9)
  - Voice of Sindh, 1992 (Box 447, Folder 10)
  - Women, 1989 1991-1994 (Box 447, Folder 11)
  - Philippines
  - Agusan del Sur--Military Operations, 1990-1992, (3 folders) (Box 447, Folder 12-14)
  - Amnesty International (AI), 1993-1994 (Box 447, Folder 15)
  - Ant-Communism/Foreign Involvement, 1989 (Box 447, Folder 16)
  - Anti-Terrorism Bill, 1996 (Box 447, Folder 17)
  - Aquino, Corazon, 1989-1990 (Box 447, Folder 18)
  - Arlen, Michael--New Yorker --Article, 1990 (Box 447, Folder 19)
  - Asia Watch (AW)
  - Correspondence, 1989-1992, (2 folders) (Box 447, Folder 20-21)
  - Work, 1988-1992, (4 folders) (Box 447, Folder 22-25)
  - Ata-Manobo, 1989 (Box 447, Folder 26)
  - Bombings/Displacement, 1989-1990 (Box 447, Folder 27)
  - Bukidnon--Illegal Logging, 1991-1992 (Box 447, Folder 28)
  - Butuan City, 1991 (Box 447, Folder 29)
  - Case Studies, 1988-1989 (Box 447, Folder 30)
  - Church
  - General, 1989-1990 (Box 447, Folder 31)
  - Persecution, 1988-1991 (Box 447, Folder 32)
  - Citizens Armed Forces Geographical Units (CAFGUs)
  - Abuses, 1989-1992 (Box 447, Folder 33)
  - General, 1989-1990 (Box 447, Folder 34)
  - Policy, 1988 1991-1992 (Box 447, Folder 35)
  - Citizens Council for Justice and Peace, 1991 (Box 447, Folder 36)
  - Claude, Richard Pierre, "Human Rights Education: The Case of the Philippines", 1991 (Box 447, Folder 37)
  - "Coddling Criminals: Militia Abuses in Mindanao, the Philippines" (Drafts), 1992 (Box 447, Folder 38)
  - Comments on the New People's Army (NPA)/National Democratic Front of the Philippines (NDF), 1989-1990 (Box 447, Folder 39)
  - Commission on Human Rights (Box 448)
  - The Philippine Experience", 1988 August (Box 448, Folder 1)
  - Reports, 1987-1990, (6 folders) (Box 448, Folder 2-7)
  - Statements, 1991 (Box 448, Folder 8)
  - Communication with Government, 1990-1992, (2 folders) (Box 448, Folder 9-10)
  - Contacts, 1987-1993 (Box 448, Folder 11)
  - Conversations, 1991 (Box 448, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence--General, 1988-1992, (3 folders) (Box 448, Folder 13-15)
  - Correspondence--Kilusang May o Uno (KMU-May 1st Movement Labor Center, 1991-1997 (Box 448, Folder 16)
  - Corruption, 1989-1990 (Box 448, Folder 17)
  - Coups
  - General, 1989-1991, (3 folders) (Box 448, Folder 18-20)
  - Post-Coup Round-up/Developments, 1989-1990 (Box 448, Folder 21)
  - Death Threats, 1989-1990 1992 (Box 448, Folder 22)
  - Demonstrations, 1989-1991 (Box 448, Folder 23)
  - Department of National Defense, 1991 (Box 448, Folder 24)
  - Disappearances, 1988-1992, (2 folders) (Box 449, Folder 1-2)
  - Displacement, 1988-1989 1991-1992 (Box 449, Folder 3)
  - Economy, 1989-1990 1992 (Box 449, Folder 4)
  - Elections, 1989-1992 (Box 449, Folder 5)
  - Eliaz Carrullo, 1991 (Box 449, Folder 6)
  - Emergency Regulations, 1989-1990 (Box 449, Folder 7)
  - Encinareal, Bernadette, 1989-1990 (Box 449, Folder 8)
  - Environment, 1989-1993 (Box 449, Folder 9)
  - Evacuations, 1989 1991 (Box 449, Folder 10)
  - Fake Surrenders, 1989 (Box 449, Folder 11)
  - Foreign Relations, 1989-1992, (3 folders) (Box 449, Folder 12-14)
  - Free Legal Assistance Group (FLAG), 1988-1992 (Box 449, Folder 15)
  - General Background, 1987-1994, (10 folders) (Box 449, Folder 16-25)
  - Gimbao, 1989-1990 (Box 450, Folder 1)
  - Government
  - Policies/Changes, 1989-1990 (Box 450, Folder 2)
  - Responses, 1991 (Box 450, Folder 3)
  - Gulf War, 1991 (Box 450, Folder 4)
  - Gun Ban/Private Armies, 1992 (Box 450, Folder 5)
  - Haribon Foundation, 1991 (Box 450, Folder 6)
  - Human Rights Code, 1989-1992, (2 folders) (Box 450, Folder 7-8)
  - Human Rights Committee, 1989 (Box 450, Folder 9)
  - Human Rights--Miscellaneous, 1990-1992 (Box 450, Folder 10)
  - Human Rights Monitors, 1988-1992, (2 folders) (Box 450, Folder 11-12)
  - Human Rights Reports, 1989 (Box 450, Folder 13)
  - Human Rights Violations (HRVs)
  - Comments on Human Rights Violations, 1988-1990 (Box 450, Folder 14)
  - Disappearances, 1991 (Box 450, Folder 15)
  - Election related, 1990-1991 (Box 450, Folder 16)
  - General, 1988-1989 1993-1994, (2 folders) (Box 450, Folder 17-18)
  - Lawyers/Human Rights Groups, 1991 (Box 450, Folder 19)
  - Mindanao, 1990 (Box 450, Folder 20)
  - Instability/Crime and Corruption, 1992 (Box 450, Folder 21)
  - International Human Rights Organizations, 1989-1992 (Box 450, Folder 22)
  - International Humanitarian Law, 1990 (Box 450, Folder 23)
  - International Solidarity News Digest, 1989-1990 1995-1997 (Box 450, Folder 24)
  - Japan, undated (Box 450, Folder 25)
  - Justice and Peace Commission-The Iceberg and the Cross: Violence Against the Church, 1990 (Box 450, Folder 26)
  - Justice and Peace Review, 1989-1992 (Box 450, Folder 27)
  - Katilingban: The Voice of the Church in Negros, 1991 1993 (Box 450, Folder 28)
  - Kawayan: Bimonthly Publication, 1991-1992 (Box 450, Folder 29)
  - Killings, 1988-1990 1992, (3 folders) (Box 450, Folder 30-32)
  - Land Confiscation--Case Materials, 1991 (Box 450, Folder 33)
  - Land Issues, 1989-1991 (Box 450, Folder 34)
  - Lawyers Committee for Human Rights, 1988-1990 (Box 450, Folder 35)
  - Legal/Legislation, 1991 (Box 450, Folder 36)
  - Legal System/Texts, 1989-1991 (Box 450, Folder 37)
  - Logging, 1988-1992 (Box 450, Folder 38)
  - Malaybalay--Killings--Case Files, 1989-1991, (2 folders) (Box 451, Folder 1-2)
  - Marag Valley, Kalinga Apayao, 1991 (Box 451, Folder 3)
  - Marcos
  - Brief of Appellant-Marcos, 1991 (Box 451, Folder 4)
  - General, 1989-1990 (Box 451, Folder 5)
  - Massacres, 1989 (Box 451, Folder 6)
  - May nila: Human Rights Monitor, 1989 October (Box 451, Folder 7)
  - Media, 1989 (Box 451, Folder 8)
  - Miles, Sara, "The Philippines and LIC: Third World Chameleon Infests Mindaneo,"The LIC [Low Intensity Conflict] Update, 1987 summer-fall (Box 451, Folder 9)
  - Military
  - General, 1987-1989 (Box 451, Folder 10)
  - Government, 1988-1990, (2 folders) (Box 451, Folder 11-12)
  - Statements, 1992 (Box 451, Folder 13)
  - Mindanao
  - Dam Project, 1989-1991 (Box 451, Folder 14)
  - General, 1988-1989 (Box 451, Folder 15)
  - Land Disputes--General, 1991 (Box 451, Folder 16)
  - Mindanao Human Rights Monitor, 1988-1990 (Box 451, Folder 17)
  - Mining, 1991 (Box 451, Folder 18)
  - Mission, 1989 September
  - Kalinga/Cordillera, 1989 (Box 451, Folder 19)
    [restricted until 2065]
  - Negros, 1989, (2 folders) (Box 451, Folder 20-21)
  - Other, 1989 (Box 451, Folder 22)
  - Zamboanga, 1989 September (Box 451, Folder 23)
  - Moro Islamic Liberation Front (MNLF), 1989-1990 (Box 451, Folder 24)
  - "Muslim Policy and Politics During the Aquino Era," undated (Box 451, Folder 25)
  - National Democratic Front of the Philippines (NDF)/New People's Army
  - Actions/Abuses, 1988-1989, (2 folders) (Box 451, Folder 26-27)
  - General, 1989-1990 (Box 451, Folder 28)
  - Statements, 1989-1990 (Box 451, Folder 29)
  - Violence, 1989-1991 (Box 451, Folder 30)
  - Negros, 1990 (Box 451, Folder 31)
  - Newsletters, 1989-1992, (2 folders) (Box 451, Folder 32-33)
  - Opposition Abuses, 1989-1990 (Box 451, Folder 34)
  - Other Organizations, 1990-1992 (Box 451, Folder 35)
  - Other Paramilitary Groups, 1989-1990 (Box 451, Folder 36)
  - Parliamentary Human Rights Group--"The CDC and Mindanao", 1983 (Box 451, Folder 37)
  - Peace Talks, 1989 1992, (2 folders) (Box 451, Folder 38-39)
  - Persecution of Military, 1989-1993 (Box 451, Folder 40)
  - Personnel--Army, 1989-1992 (Box 451, Folder 41)
  - Philippine Alliance of Human Rights Advocates, 1993-1995 (Box 452, Folder 1)
  - Philippine Human Rights Information Center, 1994 (Box 452, Folder 2)
  - Philippine Human Rights Monitor, 1989-1991 (Box 452, Folder 3)
  - Philippine International Center for Human Rights--Annual Report, 1991 (Box 452, Folder 4)
  - Philippine Logs, 1989-1994 (Box 452, Folder 5)
  - Philippine News Survey, 1993-1995 (Box 452, Folder 6)
  - Philippine Solidarity Groups, 1991 (Box 452, Folder 7)
  - Philippine Witness, 1990-1994 (Box 452, Folder 8)
  - Philippines Development Briefing, 1994-1995 (Box 452, Folder 9)
  - Police, 1989-1990 (Box 452, Folder 10)
  - Political Detainees, 1991-1992 (Box 452, Folder 11)
  - Political Prisoners
  - General, 1992-1993 (Box 452, Folder 12)
  - Political Prisoners of Our Time--Task Force Detainees of the Philippines, 1989 November (Box 452, Folder 13)
  - Political Situation, 1990-1992 (Box 452, Folder 14)
  - Press, 1988-1993, (2 folders) (Box 452, Folder 15-16)
  - Prisons/Prisoners, 1989-1992 (Box 452, Folder 17)
  - Progress Notes--Medical Action Group 1990-1995 (Box 452, Folder 18)
  - Protest--Protestant Lawyers League of the Philippines (PLLP), 1989 1991 (Box 452, Folder 19)
  - Publications--Miscellaneous, 1991-1995 (Box 452, Folder 20)
  - Rano Massacre, 1989 (Box 452, Folder 21)
  - Recent Cases--not acted upon, 1989-1992 (Box 452, Folder 22)
  - Refugees
  - General, 1990 (Box 452, Folder 23)
  - Philippine First Asylum Camp (Palawan)--Cases, 1992 (Box 452, Folder 24)
  - Regional Council on Human Rights in Asia, 1982-1988 (Box 452, Folder 25)
  - Rights Clips--NPA/Government, 1991 (Box 452, Folder 26)
  - Sipalay Incident, 1989 (Box 452, Folder 27)
  - South Cotabato (Box 453)
  - Case Files, 1990-1991 (Box 453, Folder 1)
  - Other, 1990-1991 (Box 453, Folder 2)
  - Statistical Yearbook, 1991 (Box 453, Folder 3)
  - Students, 1989-1990 (Box 453, Folder 4)
  - Surigao del Sur Case Files, 1990-1991 (Box 453, Folder 5)
  - Task Force Detainees of the Philippines--Philippine Human Rights Update, 1988-1997, (3 folders) (Box 453, Folder 6-8)
  - Torture, 1988-1989 1991-1992 (Box 453, Folder 9)
  - Trade and Aid, 1988-1992, (2 folders) (Box 453, Folder 10-11)
  - Trade Unions/Labor Rights, 1987-1993, (3 folders) (Box 454, Folder 1-3)
  - Tribal/Ethnic Groups, 1989-1991 (Box 454, Folder 4)
  - Trip to--Friedman, Julie, 1992
  - Correspondence, 1991, (2 folders) (Box 454, Folder 5-6)
  - FFM--Prep's, 1991-1992 (Box 454, Folder 7)
  - Itinerary--Maps, 1992 (Box 454, Folder 8)
  - United Nations, 1988-1989 (Box 454, Folder 9)
  - United States
  - Bush Report, 1991 (Box 454, Folder 10)
  - Congressional Advocacy, 1989-1992 (Box 454, Folder 11)
  - Government Correspondence, 1991 (Box 454, Folder 12)
  - Qualye's Visit, 1989 (Box 454, Folder 13)
  - Relations with U.S., 1989-1991 (Box 454, Folder 14)
  - Women, 1985 (Box 454, Folder 15)
  - Singapore
  - Amnesty International (AI)
  - Canada, 1989-1990 (Box 454, Folder 16)
  - Urgent Action, 1991-1992 (Box 454, Folder 17)
  - Asia Watch (AW)
  - Administration Statements, 1988-1990 (Box 454, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 454, Folder 19)
  - Work, 1989-1990 (Box 454, Folder 20)
  - Casey, Michael--Articles re, press control in Singapore and Malaysia, 1993 (Box 454, Folder 21)
  - Cheng, Vincent--Court Documents, 1989, (3 folders (Box 454, Folder 22-24)
  - Chia Thye Poh, 1989-1991 (Box 454, Folder 25)
  - Commonwealth Law Conference, 1990 (Box 455, Folder 1)
  - Communication w/Government, 1989-1990 (Box 455, Folder 2)
  - Contacts, 1989-1991 (Box 455, Folder 3)
  - Contemplacion, Flor--Death Sentence, 1995 (Box 455, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1989-1990, (2 folders) (Box 455, Folder 5-6)
  - Death Penalty, 1994-1995 (Box 455, Folder 7)
  - Demonstrations, 1989 (Box 455, Folder 8)
  - Draft Reports, includes interviews, 1988-1989 (Box 455, Folder 9)
  - Economist /Business Times, 1993-1994 (Box 455, Folder 10)
  - Emergency Committee for Human Rights in Singapore (ECHRS), 1989-1990 (Box 455, Folder 11)
  - Far Eastern Economic Review (FEER)
  - Case, 1987-1989 1991, (2 folders) (Box 455, Folder 12-13)
  - Letters, 1989-1990 (Box 455, Folder 14)
  - Fay, Michael--Corporal Punishment, 1994 (Box 455, Folder 15)
  - Foreign Relations, 1989-1990 (Box 455, Folder 16)
  - General, 1989-1990 (Box 455, Folder 17)
  - Human Rights and Press Freedom--General, 1993-1994 (Box 455, Folder 18)
  - Human Rights Report on Singapore, 1993, (2 folders) (Box 455, Folder 19-20)
  - Human Rights Violations, 1989-1990 (Box 455, Folder 21)
  - Internal Security Act (ISA), 1989-1990 (Box 455, Folder 22)
  - International Human Rights Organizations, 1987-1989 (Box 455, Folder 23)
  - Jeyaretnam's Court Cases, 1989, (2 folders) (Box 455, Folder 24-25)
  - Killings, 1989 (Box 455, Folder 26)
  - Labor, 1989-1990 (Box 456, Folder 1)
  - Lee Kuan Yew v. Derek Gwyn Davies--Hearing Transcript, 1989, (11 folders) (Box 456, Folder 2-12)
  - Lee Kuan Yew vs. The News: A History, undated (Box 456, Folder 13)
  - Legal System/Texts, 1984-1990 1992, (4 folders) (Box 456, Folder 14-17)
  - Lester, Anthony (Queen's Counsel), 1989 (Box 456, Folder 18)
  - Lingle, Chris (American economist), 1995 (Box 456, Folder 19)
  - Military and Government, 1988-1991, (3 folders) (Box 456, Folder 20-22)
  - Missions/Visits, 1988 (Box 456, Folder 23)
  - Parliamentary Debates, 1988-1989 (Box 456, Folder 24)
  - Paul, E.C., "Obstacles to Demonstrations in Singapore", 1992 (Box 456, Folder 25)
  - Policing the Internet, 1995 (Box 456, Folder 26)
  - Press, 1989 (Box 456, Folder 27)
  - Press Releases, 1989 (Box 457, Folder 1)
  - Prison Conditions, 1988-1990 1992 (Box 457, Folder 2)
  - Seow, Francis T.--Case, 1988-1990 (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Singapore/Malaysia, 1989-1990 (Box 457, Folder 4)
  - Singapore Project--Human Rights Mission Report, 1987 (Box 457, Folder 5)
    - Statutes/Acts
    - Broadcasting and Television Act, 1963 (Box 457, Folder 6)
    - Cinematograph Films Act, 1954 (Box 457, Folder 7)
    - Commissions of Inquiry Act, 1985 (Box 457, Folder 8)
    - Complaints of Allegations of Executive Interference in the Judiciary, 1987 (Box 457, Folder 9)
    - Constitution of the Republic of Singapore, 1980 (Box 457, Folder 10)
    - Criminal Law (Temporary Provisions) Act, 1985 (Box 457, Folder 11)
    - Employment Act, 1985 (Box 457, Folder 12)
    - Films Act, 1981 (Box 457, Folder 13)
    - Gazette, 1964 (Box 457, Folder 14)
    - Government Gazette Acts Supplement, 1986 (Box 457, Folder 15)
    - Housing and Development Act, 1985 (Box 457, Folder 16)
    - Industrial Relations Act, 1985 (Box 457, Folder 17)
    - Internal Security Act, 1965 (Box 457, Folder 18)
    - Judicial Committee Act, 1985 (Box 457, Folder 19)
    - Legal Aid and Advice Act, 1985 (Box 457, Folder 20)
    - Legal Profession Act, 1986 (Box 457, Folder 21)
      - Legal Profession (Amendment) Act, 1976 (Box 457, Folder 22)
      - Legal Profession (Amendment) Act, 1979 (Box 457, Folder 23)
      - Newspaper and Printing Presses Act, 1974 (Box 457, Folder 24)
      - Official Secrets Act, 1935 (Box 457, Folder 25)
      - Parliament (Privileges, Immunities and Powers) Act, 1962 (Box 457, Folder 26)
      - Parliamentary Elections Act, 1985 (Box 457, Folder 27)
      - Prevention of Crimes Act, 1940 (Box 457, Folder 28)
      - Printers and Publishers Act, 1835 (Box 457, Folder 29)
      - Printing Presses Act, 1955 (Box 457, Folder 30)
      - Public Service Commission Act, 1985 (Box 457, Folder 31)
      - Sedition Act, 1964 (Box 457, Folder 32)
      - Singapore Broadcasting Corporation Act, 1985 (Box 457, Folder 33)
      - Societies Act, 1967 (Box 457, Folder 34)
      - Status of the Republic of Singapore Act, 1985 (Box 457, Folder 35)
      - Subordinate Courts Act, 1985 (Box 457, Folder 36)
      - Supreme Court of Judicature Act, 1986 (Box 457, Folder 37)
      - Table of Contents of Acts, undated (Box 457, Folder 38)
      - Telecommunications Authority of Singapore (Box 457, Folder 39)
      - Trade Disputes Act, 1985 (Box 457, Folder 40)
      - Trade Unions Act, 1967 (Box 457, Folder 41)
        - Trade Unions (Amendment) Act, 1973 (Box 457, Folder 42)
        - Trade Unions (Amendment) Act, 1977 (Box 457, Folder 43)
        - Trade Unions (Amendment) Act, 1982 (Box 457, Folder 44)
        - Undesirable Publications Act, 1967 (Box 457, Folder 45)
        - General